Every breath you take
and every move you make
Every bond you break
Every step you take
I'll be watching you
Every single day
and every word you say
Every game you play, every night
you stay, I'll be watching you
Oh can't you see
you belong to me
My poor heart aches
with every step you take
Every move you make,
and every vow you break
Every smile you fake, every claim
you steak, I'll be watching you
Since you've been gone
I've been lost without a trace
I dream at night
I can only see your face
I look around but its
you I can't replace
I feel so cold and I long
for your embrace
I keep crying baby baby please
Oh can't you see
you belong to me
How my poor heart aches
with every step you take
Every move you make,
and every vow you break
Every smile you fake, every claim
you steak, I'll be watching you
Every move you make, every step
you take, I'll be watching you
I'll be watching you
Every breath you take
and every move you make
Every bond you break
- Every step you take (I'll be watching)
- I'll be watching you
Every single day
every word you say
Every game you play, every night
you stay (I'll be watching you)
Every move you make,
and every vow you break
Every smile you fake, every claim
you steak (I'll be watching you)
Every single day, every word you say
Every game you play, every night
you stay (I'll be watching you)